

# CJIES TAN

FRONT END ENGINEER

# CONTACT

### Name:

Xi Jie Tan 陳熙杰

### Email:

cijies@gmail.com

#### Phone:

+886-978-109-929

### Website:

https://cjies.com

### Nationality:

Malaysian

## **EDUCATION**

# **Computer Science B.Eng**

National Cheng Kung University Tainan, Taiwan (2010 - 2014) Major in web development and UI design.

# **SKILLS**

### Frontend

Javascript/ES6+ - Proficient CSS/Sass/CSS-in-JS - Proficient React/Flow/Typescript - Proficient Ionic/angularJS - Intermediate

### Backend

node.js - Proficient Django/python - Intermediate Docker - Intermediate Jenkins/Travis CI - Intermediate GraphQL - Intermediate

# Languages

English - Professional Proficiency Mandarin - Native Cantonese - Fluent Japanese - Basic (N3)

## **PROFILE**



I am a software engineer with 5+ years experience, mainly skilled in web application development (React, Flow, Webpack, GraphQL, Docker) and mobile web app development (Ionic, Cordova, React and etc).

I am interesting in trying new ideas that can make people's live easier, like improving dev process in more agile way. I am also adaptive and welcome challenges, whether it is cross-platform or different form factor products, or customization requirements from different partners.

# **EXPERIENCES**

# **Senior Front End Engineer III** Appier, Taipei

Jul 2017 - Present

- Led and managed dashboard frontend team in the creation of frontend web application and web SDK to support business operations and requirements.
- Roled as Agile Coach, led the team to hit feature/function deadlines with stable team velocity and strong motivation.
- Rebuilt frontend web application from the ground up, developed and designed related components and build tools in monolithic architecture.
- Introduced type systems and adopted into team's product progressively, which aimed to reduce static type errors before build and secure the correctness of React applications.

Tech skills: React/Redux, Flow, styled-components, Django, GraphQL, etc

# Front End Developer iCHEF Co. Ltd., Taipei

Mar 2016 - Jun2017

- Designed and coded a large in-house component library for react apps.
- Created a cross-platform deploy tool to deliver products easier and faster.
- Participated in many community-organized meetups to sharing experiences and new findings.

Tech skills: React/Redux, Django, Electron, Docker, etc

- Developed a web CMS application for restaurant POS.

### **Front End Engineer**

Sep 2014 - Feb 2016

Galaxy Software Services, Taipei

- Positioned as main front-end engineer in design team.
- Architectured a common build scripts for web development.
- Developed a hybrid mobile application which support iOS & Android platform.
- Worked with software developers from different departments to build a large scaled software application.

Tech skills: Ionic, angularJS, Cordova, Kendo, .net MVC